#This dictionary is used to make a question bank for the dad joke quiz game

#"question" is the key and "answer" is the value
question_bank = { 
    "question": "What do sprinters eat before a race?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"nothing they fast", 
    "hint": "what is the religious practice of not eating"
    }

{
    "question": "Air use to be free at the gas station, now its a $1.50. You know why?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer": "inflation", 
    "hint":"the opposite of deflation"
}

{
    "question": "How did the man on the moon cut his hair?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer": "he eclipse it",
    "hint":"what is it called when the sun covers the moon"
} 

{
    "question": "What do a tick and the Eiffel Tower have in common?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"They're both Paris sites", 
    "hint":"where is the Eiffel tower located"
}

{
    "question": "What do you call a fish wearing a bowtie?",
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer": "Sofishticated", 
    "hint":"what is a word for a knowledgeable fashionable person"
}

{
    "question": "If April showers bring May flowers, what do May flowers bring?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer": "Pilgrims", 
    "hint":"who sailed to the united states"
}

{
    "question": "What do you call a factory that makes okay products?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"A satisfactory", 
    "hint":"what is another way to to say you did a good job"
}

{
    "question": "What did the janitor say when he jumped out of the closet?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"Supplies", 
    "hint":"____ & demand"
}

{
    "question":"What did one wall say to the other?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer": "I'll meet you at the corner", 
    "hint":"what is it called when two edges meet"
}

{
    "question":"What did the zero say to the eight?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer" :"That belt looks good on you",
    "hint":"what do you use to hold your pants up, that is not suspenders"
}

{
    "question": "What do you call a poor Santa Claus?",
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer": "St. Nickel-less", 
    "hint":"st. Nick"
}

{
    "question":"What did one hat say to the other?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"Stay here! I'm going on ahead", 
    "hint":"where do hats go on a person"
}

{
    "question": "Why was the PowerPoint presentation so desperate to cross the road?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"Because he badly wanted to go the other slide",
    "hint":"what is a powerpoint presontation made of"
}

{
    "question":"Why did everyone tell the new computer teacher that he was always extremely confused on Twitter?",
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"It was probably because he didn't follow", 
    "hint":"how do you stay up to date with a page on twitter"
}

{
    "question":"What is the only reason why a car made by computer manufacturers doesn't last for a very long time?",
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"It is perhaps because they have hard drives", 
    "hint":"if your computer doesn't have a SD it has a ___"
}

{
    "question":"Why was the computer scientist very upset when his computer got affected by a virus?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"Because it was a terminal illness", 
    "hint": "What is another word for console or command line"
}

{
    "question":"Which animal is the absolute expert in navigating the internet? A spider.", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"Because spiders know all about the web", 
    "hint":"what do spiders use to trap their prey"
}

{
    "question":"Why did the functions stop calling each other?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"Because they had constant arguments",
    "hint":"what goes inside a function"
}

{
    "question":"What do you call a skinny ghost?",
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"BOOLEAN",
    "hint": "what are the AND, OR, NOT or AND NOT operators used for"
}

{
    "question":"Why does Yoda’s code always crash?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"Because there is no try", 
    "hint": "do or do not"
}

{
    "question":"Why do anarchists like functional programming?", 
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"Because it has no state", 
    "hint":"what are New jersey, ohio, nevada"
}

{
    "question":"What’s the second movie about a database engineer called?",
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"SQL",
    "hint":"domain-specific language used in programming and designed for managing data "
}

{
    "question":"Why didn't the client tip the server?",
    "multiple choice": "A)",
    "answer":"Because they didn't have enough cache", 
    "hint":"something in computer science that stores data so that future requests for that data can be served faster;"
}